FABIYI OLUWATOSIN STEPHEN

Personal Details

Address: No 8, Elere, Olupoyi street, Bembo road, Ibadan, Oyo State.

Email: xoftsteve123@gmail.com

Telephone no: 08034476735, 08136424249

Objectives

Hardworking and experienced with several years of experience serving as a supportive and integral employee in high volume client settings. Experienced in creating schedules, making appointments, selling products, and providing clients with optimal customer's service. Bringing forth the ability to manage front desk settings with poise and grace, in addition to manage a variety of administrative duties. Eager to join a new team of people, and assist them as a dedicated and passionate employee.

NYSC Status: Completed

Work Experience

1. Infinity Estate and Properties

(Field Manager)

January 2022- June 2022

• Oversee, supervise and evaluate employees on the site.

2. Flava Logistics

(Logistics Supervisor)

July 2022 – December 2022

- Oversee activities with regards to the acquisition, repair and preventive maintenance and replacement of fleet to meet company's logistics needs.
- Follow up with finance to ensure updated and adequate documents
- Oversee all dispatch processing and handover activities, proof of delivery, goods received notes etc.

3. Government College Ibadan

January 2021- December 2021

(NYSC Oyo State)

4. Xoft Laundry Services

January 2020 - December 2020

(Laundry Supervisor)

• I was the laundry supervisor and attendant

5. Icon Jones hotel- Ibadan

January 2019 - December 2019

Housekeeping Supervisor

- I was the housekeeper supervisor and assistant
- 6. **Ministry of Physical Planning- Akure** April 2016 September 2016 (Industrial Training)
 - Provided clients with supreme service and worked collaboratively to achieve their wants.
 - · Worked with clients to assess their needs and desires
 - · Assisted clients with designs processing.

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Urban and Regional Planning Obafemi Awolowo University Ile-Ife, Nigeria

February 2020

Skills

- · Assistant Manager Experience
- · Housekeeping Management
- · Digital marketing
- Front Desk
- Caregiving
- Good Communication
- Goal Getter
- Smart
- Intelligent
- · Critical Thinker
- · Problem Solver

Additional Information

- Computer literate
- Efficient and agile
- Good qualities of leadership
- Reliable, honest, and friendly